const yeardata = [
  // History
  { Id: '0', Question: 'was the first modern Olympic Games held in Athens', Answer: '1896' },
  { Id: '1', Question: 'was the Magna Carta signed', Answer: '1215' },
  { Id: '2', Question: 'was the Great Fire of London', Answer: '1666' },
  { Id: '3', Question: 'did Michael Jackson die', Answer: '2009' },
  { Id: '4', Question: 'was the film, Jaws, released as a summer blockbuster by Steven Spielberg', Answer: '1975' },
  { Id: '5', Question: 'was the first ever Winter Olympics', Answer: '1924' },
  { Id: '6', Question: 'was Disney founded', Answer: '1923' },
  { Id: '7', Question: 'was the declaration of independence, of the United States of America', Answer: '1776' },
  { Id: '8', Question: 'was the start of the French Revolution', Answer: '1789' },
  { Id: '9', Question: "was the controversial 'Hand of God' goal, by Diego Maradona, in the World Cup", Answer: '1986' },
  { Id: '10', Question: "was the best selling single 'White Christmas' by Bing Crosby released", Answer: '1942' },
  { Id: '11', Question: 'was the beginning of the First World War', Answer: '1914' },
  { Id: '12', Question: 'was the Chernobyl disaster', Answer: '1986' },
  { Id: '13', Question: 'was the first iPhone released', Answer: '2007' },
  { Id: '14', Question: 'was the first World Cup in football played', Answer: '1930' },
  { Id: '15', Question: 'was the first Harry Potter book released', Answer: '1997' },
  { Id: '16', Question: 'did Apollo 11 with Neil Armstrong land on the moon', Answer: '1969' },
  { Id: '17', Question: 'was the charity supergroup Band Aid formed to raise money for famine relief', Answer: '1984' },
  { Id: '18', Question: 'was the World Wide Web invented', Answer: '1990' },
  { Id: '19', Question: 'was Google founded', Answer: '1998' },
  { Id: '20', Question: 'was the Munich Air Disaster with the Manchester United football team on board  ', Answer: '1958' },
  { Id: '21', Question: "was the single 'Bridge over Troubled Water' by Simon and Garfunkel released", Answer: '1970' },
  { Id: '22', Question: 'did apartheid end in South Africa', Answer: '1994' },
  { Id: '23', Question: 'was the attack on the World Trade Centre in New York', Answer: '2001' },
  { Id: '24', Question: 'did Usain Bolt set the current 100 metre world record of 9.58 seconds in Berlin', Answer: '2009' },
  { Id: '25', Question: 'did the Titantic sink on her maiden voyage', Answer: '1912' },
  { Id: '26', Question: 'was the beginning of the Great Famine in Ireland', Answer: '1845' },
  { Id: '27', Question: "was Madonna's first number one hit - Like a Virgin - released", Answer: '1984' },
  { Id: '28', Question: 'did Bob Beamon shatter the long jump world record in Mexico City', Answer: '1968' },
  { Id: '29', Question: 'was the Easter Rising in Ireland', Answer: '1916' },
  { Id: '30', Question: 'did construction start on the Sagrada Familia cathedral in Barcelona', Answer: '1882' },
  { Id: '31', Question: 'did the Iraq war begin', Answer: '2003' },
  { Id: '32', Question: 'did South Africa win the Rugby World Cup with Nelson Mandela presenting the trophy', Answer: '1995' },
  { Id: '33', Question: 'was the first space shuttle, called Columbia, launched', Answer: '1981' },
  { Id: '34', Question: 'was the fall of the Berlin Wall', Answer: '1989' },
  { Id: '35', Question: 'was the end of the Second World War', Answer: '1945' },
  { Id: '36', Question: 'did Michael Phelps win an incredible 8 gold medals at one olympics in swimming', Answer: '2008' },
  { Id: '37', Question: 'was the attack on the United States naval base in Pearl Harbour', Answer: '1941' },
  { Id: '38', Question: 'was the start of the Cold War', Answer: '1947' },
  { Id: '39', Question: "was the single 'Thinking Out Loud' by Ed Sheeran released", Answer: '2014' },
  { Id: '40', Question: 'was the first ever Super Bowl in American Football played', Answer: '1967' },
  { Id: '41', Question: 'was the first powered flight by the Wright brothers', Answer: '1903' },
  { Id: '42', Question: 'saw the collapse of the Soviet Union into fifteen separate countries', Answer: '1991' },
  { Id: '43', Question: 'was John F. Kennedy assassinated', Answer: '1963' },
  { Id: '44', Question: 'did Jesse Owens win 4 gold medals in the Olympic Games in Berlin', Answer: '1936' },
  { Id: '45', Question: 'saw the end of the Vietnam War with the fall of Saigon', Answer: '1975' },
  { Id: '46', Question: 'was the Battle of Britain', Answer: '1940' },
  { Id: '47', Question: 'was the start of the Korean War when North Korea invaded South Korea', Answer: '1950' },
  { Id: '48', Question: 'was the Roswell Unidentified Flying Object incident', Answer: '1947' },
  { Id: '49', Question: 'was the start of the Khmer Rouge regime in Cambodia which led to mass genocide', Answer: '1975' },
  { Id: '50', Question: 'did Princess Diana die', Answer: '1997' },
  { Id: '51', Question: 'did the Gulf War begin', Answer: '1990' },
  { Id: '52', Question: 'was Facebook founded', Answer: '2004' },
  { Id: '53', Question: 'did Brazil win their first world cup in football', Answer: '1958' },
  { Id: '54', Question: 'did Margaret Thatcher become Prime Minister', Answer: '1979' },
  { Id: '55', Question: "did Emily Davison throw herself under the King's horse on Derby Day", Answer: '1913' },
  { Id: '56', Question: 'was the Irish Free State Treaty signed', Answer: '1921' },
  { Id: '57', Question: 'was the start of the UK General Strike', Answer: '1926' },
  { Id: '58', Question: "was the world's first non-stop transatlantic flight", Answer: '1927' },
  { Id: '59', Question: 'was the film Titanic released', Answer: '1997' },
  { Id: '60', Question: 'did Adolf Hitler become German Chancellor', Answer: '1933' },
  { Id: '61', Question: 'did the first official Ryder Cup take place', Answer: '1927' },
  { Id: '62', Question: 'did King Edward the Eighth abdicate to marry Wallis Simpson', Answer: '1936' },
  { Id: '63', Question: "was the book, 'The Da Vinci Code' by Dan Brown released", Answer: '2003' },
  { Id: '64', Question: 'did Argentina win their first world cup in football', Answer: '1978' },
  { Id: '65', Question: 'was Apple founded', Answer: '1976' },
  { Id: '66', Question: 'was the mass evacuation of Allied Forces from Dunkirk', Answer: '1940' },
  { Id: '67', Question: "did the United States launch the world's first nuclear subramine", Answer: '1954' },
  { Id: '68', Question: 'did a Soviet cosmonaut become the first man in space', Answer: '1961' },
  { Id: '69', Question: 'was the first Grand National at Aintree', Answer: '1839' },
  { Id: '70', Question: "was the single 'I will always love you' by Whitney Houston released", Answer: '1992' },
  { Id: '71', Question: 'was the Berlin Wall erected, sealing the border between East and West Berlin', Answer: '1961' },
  { Id: '72', Question: 'was the Cuban Missile Crisis, a confrontation between the Soviet Union, Cuba and the United States', Answer: '1962' },
  { Id: '73', Question: "did Martin Luther King deliver his famous, 'I have a dream', speech", Answer: '1963' },
  { Id: '74', Question: "was the single 'Thriller' by Michael Jackson released", Answer: '1983' },
  { Id: '75', Question: 'did a coal tip bury hundreds of children in Aberfan, South Wales', Answer: '1966' },
  { Id: '76', Question: 'did Michael Spitz set a then world record of 7 gold medals at one olympics', Answer: '1972' },
  { Id: '77', Question: 'did Donald Campbell die attempting to set a water speed record in Bluebird', Answer: '1967' },
  { Id: '78', Question: 'was Amazon founded', Answer: '1994' },
  { Id: '79', Question: 'was the Six Day War, a conflict fought between Israeli and Arab Forces across large areas of the Middle East', Answer: '1967' },
  { Id: '80', Question: 'did Elvis Presley die', Answer: '1977' },
  { Id: '81', Question: 'did Concorde make its maiden flight', Answer: '1969' },
  { Id: '82', Question: "did Wayde van Niekerk from South Africa beat Michael Johnson's 400 metre world record", Answer: '2016' },
  { Id: '83', Question: 'was the film E. T. - the Extra Terrestial released', Answer: '1982' },
  { Id: '84', Question: 'did British troops shoot protesters in Northern Ireland, in an event known as Bloody Sunday', Answer: '1972' },
  { Id: '85', Question: "was the single 'Someone like you' by Adele released", Answer: '2011' },
  { Id: '86', Question: 'did Nixon become the first president of the United States to resign from office', Answer: '1974' },
  { Id: '87', Question: 'was the world famous racehorse Shergar kidnapped', Answer: '1983' },
  { Id: '88', Question: "did George Lucas release the film 'Star Wars'", Answer: '1977' },
  { Id: '89', Question: 'was the Heysel Stadium Disaster, before the European Cup Final between Juventus and Liverpool', Answer: '1985' },
  { Id: '90', Question: 'did Space Shuttle Challenger disintegrate 73 seconds into its flight', Answer: '1986' },
  { Id: '91', Question: 'was the Zeebrugge Ferry Disaster, when the Herald of Free Enterprise car ferry capsized', Answer: '1987' },
  { Id: '92', Question: 'was the Hillsborough Disaster, where 96 innocent people lost their lives at a football match', Answer: '1989' },
  { Id: '93', Question: 'did Bobby Jones make sporting history by winning the Grand Slam in golf', Answer: '1930' },
  { Id: '94', Question: 'did the Beatles have their first number 1 hit with From Me to You on the Official UK Singles Chart', Answer: '1963' },
  { Id: '95', Question: "was the Tiananmen Square Massacre, where soldiers from the Chinese People's Army massacred hundreds", Answer: '1989' },
  { Id: '96', Question: 'did Italy win their first world cup in football', Answer: '1934' },
  { Id: '97', Question: "was the epic film, 'Gone with the Wind', released", Answer: '1939' },
  { Id: '98', Question: 'was Nelson Mandela released from prison', Answer: '1990' },
  { Id: '99', Question: 'was the Indian Ocean Earthquake and Tsunami Disaster', Answer: '2004' },
  { Id: '100', Question: "was the single 'Bohemian Rhapsody' by Queen released", Answer: '1975' },
  { Id: '101', Question: 'did the 17 year old Pele score a stunning goal as Brazil beat Sweden in the World Cup Final', Answer: '1958' },
  { Id: '102', Question: 'did Hurricane Katrina devastate New Orleans', Answer: '2005' },
  { Id: '103', Question: 'was Barack Obama elected as the first Black President of the United States', Answer: '2008' },
  { Id: '104', Question: 'did Red Rum win his first grand national race', Answer: '1973' },
  { Id: '105', Question: 'did Nelson Mandela die', Answer: '2013' },
  { Id: '106', Question: "was the American musical film 'Grease' released", Answer: '1978' },
];


const data = Object.freeze({

  DATA: yeardata,

});

export default data;
